<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>League of Robot Runners</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:3000/Events/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:3000/Events/"/>
 <updated>2024-02-08T18:38:17-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:3000</id>
 <author>
   <name>Mark Otto</name>
   <email>markdotto@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>The League of Robot Runners The 2024 Virtual Event</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:3000/2024/02/08/call_virtual_event/"/>
   <updated>2024-02-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:3000/Events/2024/02/08/call_virtual_event</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;call-for-participation-league-of-robot-runners-2024-virtual-event&quot;&gt;Call For Participation: League of Robot Runners 2024 Virtual Event&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello Robot Runners!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce an upcoming virtual event to celebrate the conclusion of the League of Robot Runners competition!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;aim&quot;&gt;Aim&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event provides a fantastic opportunity for participants to share their experiences, insights, and the innovative approaches that made this competition truly remarkable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;event-highlights&quot;&gt;Event Highlights:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keynote from Amazon:&lt;/strong&gt; We will invite keynote speakers from Amazon to talk about the importance of the problem.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results Recap and Announcement of Winners:&lt;/strong&gt; Discover the outstanding achievements and noteworthy outcomes of the competition.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Participant Talks:&lt;/strong&gt; Each participant will have a 15-minute slot to present their experiences and insights. We encourage you to share your strategies, challenges overcome, and the lessons learned during the competition.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paper and Video Presentation:&lt;/strong&gt; Participants are invited to prepare a paper along with a short 5-minute video presentation to accompany their talks. This provides an excellent opportunity to delve deeper into your methodologies and showcase your achievements visually.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;date-and-time&quot;&gt;Date and Time:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date:&lt;/strong&gt; 21st May (tentative)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; Central Europe Time (tentative)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We look forward to your participation in this virtual event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should you have any questions or need further information, please feel free to reach out to [Organizer’s Contact Information].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for making the League of Robot Runners a resounding success, and we can’t wait to see you at the virtual event!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The League of Robot Runners The 2024  Main round</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:3000/2023/04/03/introducing-robotRunners/"/>
   <updated>2023-04-03T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:3000/Events/2023/04/03/introducing-robotRunners</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The League of Robot Runners, sponsored by Amazon Robotics, is a competition where participants tackle one of the most complex optimization challenges: the coordination of multiple moving robots, which is important for industrial applications such as warehouse logistics, transportation and advanced manufacturing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-mission&quot;&gt;The Mission&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your mission, should you choose to accept it, is to navigate a team of robotic errand runners, completing tasks as efficiently as possible, while subject to computational constraints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simplified versions of such problems appear in the research literature under the name Multi-Agent Path Finding, Multi-Robot Path Planning and many others besides. In this competition we bridge the gap between academia and industry by identifying the core combinatorial challenges that make these problems difficult to solve in practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participating in the competition means not only demonstrating your skills against the best in the field but also contributing to the establishment of new benchmarks and algorithmic baselines. You’ll have the chance to make a tangible impact on the progression of the research field, with the possibility of your innovative solutions being adopted by the wider community. Moreover, your involvement will help increase attention to this critical problem and contribute to the growth of our community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../warehouse-demo_landing2.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Example&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;eligibility-and-prizes&quot;&gt;Eligibility and Prizes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participation is open to individuals and teams of individuals from any discipline and background and from any geographic location. Financial prizes (in $USD) are available for distinguished performance:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other notable performances (2nd, 3rd place in each category) will be recognised with a certificate. Register and submit your implementation before the submission deadline to be eligible!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To lower participation costs we also have a limited number of training awards. Distributed according to merit, these awards come in the form of AWS credits (up to $1000 USD), which can be used to help with the offline development of computational models.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;important-dates&quot;&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Warm up Round: 13th July - 18th August&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Main Round: 19th August - 31st October 30th November (extended!)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Results Announcement: 20th November December (extended!)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
